Contact

tikieb@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/takarabutler-rn-msn-mha-ccm-35237963 (LinkedIn) gmail.com (Personal)

Top Skills

Healthcare

EMR

Critical Care

Languages

English

Takara Butler RN, MSN, MHA, CCM

Registered Nurse at East Jefferson General Hospital Baton Rouge, Louisiana Area

Summary

I am a native of Baton Rouge, LA and dual masters prepared registered nurse with diverse nursing experience ranging from emergency/critical care, hospice, home health, education, disaster relief, case management and vascular nursing. I love specialty nursing and am pursing certification in vascular access. My desire is to advance my practice as a nurse anesthetist. I am very diverse within my profession and never self limiting to one realm. My desire is to educate, advocate, and promote health through health literacy. Community nursing deeply connects to me and am willing to work with anyone to help end health disparities within Louisiana and abroad.

I am the business owner of The Resouce Center, which is an established nonprofit, 501c3 organization. The Resource Center's primary focus is to provide health education to at risk minorities through preventative teaching.

Feel free to connect with me at Takara.butler@gmail.com

Experience

East Jefferson General Hospital Registered Nurse April 2018 - Present (2 years 3 months) Metairie, Louisiana

PICC Nurse

American Mobile Healthcare Travel Registered Nurse January 2018 - April 2018 (4 months) Baton Rouge, Louisiana Aya Healthcare
Travel Registered Nurse
October 2017 - December 2017 (3 months)

Louisiana

contract travel nurse: ER, Case Management, Nurse Manager

Ochsner Health System
Registered Nurse
May 2017 - October 2017 (6 months)
Baton Rouge, Louisiana

ER Nurse

UnitedHealth Group

3 years 4 months

Manager

May 2016 - October 2017 (1 year 6 months)

Metairie, Louisiana

Manage Louisiana Case Management Team

Case Manager

July 2014 - May 2016 (1 year 11 months)

Baton Rouge General Medical Center

9 years 1 month

Registered Nurse ER Midcity
August 2008 - August 2014 (6 years 1 month)

Emergency Room

ER Tech

August 2005 - August 2008 (3 years 1 month)

Louisiana Healthcare Connections Inc. Case Manager March 2013 - May 2014 (1 year 3 months)

Baton Rouge, Louisiana

Southern Care Hospice Case Manager August 2013 - February 2014 (7 months)

Prarieville, LA

Education

University of Phoenix

Masters of Science in Nursing & Healthcare Administration, Nursing Administration · (2014 - 2017)

Southern University and Agricultural and Mechanical College at Baton Rouge

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (2005 - 2008)

Southern University and Agricultural and Mechanical College at Baton Rouge

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2005 - 2008)

Southeastern Louisiana University

Nursing Education · (2001 - 2005)